Guide to the United States Catholic China Bureau Records
Yale University Divinity School Library
- Periodicals, 1976-2011; Series I
  - Faith
    - "Faith 10-Day" No. 304 (Jun 10, 2007) - No. 338 (May 20, 2008) (incomplete) (Box 64, Folder 5)
    - "Faith 20-Day" No. 314 (Jan 20, 2007); Special page (Feb 1, 2008) (Box 64, Folder 6)
  - Foreign Affairs
    - 1997-1998 (Box 78, Folder 4)
    - 2000 - 2001, #1 (Box 78, Folder 5)
    - 2001, #2 - 2002, #1 (Box 79, Folder 1)
    - 2002, #2-3 (Box 79, Folder 2)
    - 2002, #4-5 (Box 79, Folder 3)
    - 2002, #6 - 2003, #3 (Box 79, Folder 4)
    - 2003, #4-5 (Box 80, Folder 1)
    - 2003, #6 - 2004, #4 (Box 80, Folder 2)
    - 2004, #5-6 (Box 80, Folder 3)
    - 2005, #1-2 (Box 80, Folder 4)
    - 2005, #3, #5 (Box 81, Folder 1)
  - Friends of the Church in China Newsletter
    Published in Witney, Oxon (United Kingdom) by The Witney Press Limited
    - No. 19 (Spring 1991)-no. 21 (Winter 1991), no. 23 (Summer 1992), no. 24 (Autumn 1992), no. 27 (Spring 1994)-no. 30 (Autumn 1995) (Box 22, Folder 122)
    - no. 31 (Spring 1996) (Box 38, Folder 338)
  - Global Affairs
    - Summer 1992 (Box 81, Folder 3)
  - The Hearth
    Published in New Haven, CT by the Friends of the Overseas Ministries Study Center
    - No. 12 (Fall 2002) (Box 39, Folder 349)
  - Holy Spirit Study Centre
    - Annual Reports, 1989, 1991, 1994 (Box 87, Folder 4)
    - Annual Reports, 1995-1997 (Box 87, Folder 5)
    - Annual Reports, 1998-1999, 2001 (Box 88, Folder 1)
    - Annual Reports, 2002, 2003, 2005 (Box 88, Folder 2)
  - In God's Image
    - 1991-1992, 1994 (Box 88, Folder 3)
  - Inside China Mainland
    Published in Taipei, Taiwan by Institute of Current China Studies
    - Vol. 12 no. 5 issue 137 (May 1990)-vol. 12 no. 9 issue 141 (Sept. 1990), vol. 12 no. 11 issue 143 (Nov. 1990)-vol. 18 no. 12 issue 216 (Dec. 1996), vol. 19 no. 2 issue 218 (Feb. 1997)-vol. 19 no. 11 issue 227 (Nov. 1997), vol. 20 no. 1 issue 229 (Jan. 1998), vol. 20 no. 3 issue 231 (Mar. 1998)-vol. 20 no. 8 issue 236 (Aug. 1998), vol. 20 no. 10 issue 238 (Oct. 1998)-vol. 21 no. 9 issue 249 (Sept. 1999), Twenty Years of Inside China Mainland: a Monthly Index 1979-1998; Also available at SML: DS 701 I55+ (Box 22–24)
  - International Bulletin of Missionary Research
    Published in New Haven, CT by Overseas Ministries Study Center
    - Vol. 25 no. 3 (Jul 2001), vol. 27 no. 3 (Jul. 2001)- no. 4 (Oct. 2003), vol. 28 no. 1 (Jan. 2004)- no.3 (Jul. 2004), vol. 29 no. 1 (Jan. 2005)- no. 4 (Oct. 2005) (Box 38, Folder 339-340)
    - Vol. 30 no. 1 (Jan. 2006)- no. 4 (Oct. 2006) (Box 53, Folder 426)
  - International Documentation Service
    Published in Italy by IDOC International
    - No. 12 (Dec. 1979) (Box 61, Folder 469)
  - International Review of Mission
    - 1981 Apr (Box 81, Folder 2)
  - Jahresbericht
    - 1990-1996 (Box 88, Folder 5)
    - 1997-2001 (Box 89, Folder 1)
    - 2002-2006 (Box 89, Folder 2)
    - 2007-2010 (Box 89, Folder 3)
  - Journal of Asian Studies
    - 1986 Feb - 1986 May (Box 90, Folder 5)
    - 1986 Aug - 1986 Nov (Box 91, Folder 1)
    - 1987 Feb (Box 83, Folder 2)
    - 1987 May (Box 83, Folder 3)
    - 1987 Aug (Box 83, Folder 4)
    - 1987 Nov (Box 83, Folder 5)
    - 1988 Feb (Box 83, Folder 6)
    - 1988 May (Box 83, Folder 7)
    - 1988 Aug (Box 84, Folder 1)
    - 1989 May (Box 84, Folder 2)
    - 1989 Aug (Box 84, Folder 3)
    - 1989 Nov (Box 84, Folder 4)
    - 1995 Feb (Box 84, Folder 5)
  - Journal of the History of Christianity in Modern China
    - 1998 (Box 81, Folder 2)
  - Linkreport (New Chinalink)
    - Winter 2005 (Box 70, Folder 1)
  - Mainland Brief
    Published in Caritas-Hong Kong by the Mainland Service Desk
    - No. 1 (Jun. 2004)- no. 5 (Jun. 2005), no. 7 (Dec. 2005) (Box 38, Folder 341)
    - No. 8 (Mar. 2006)- no. 11 (Dec. 2006) (Box 53, Folder 427)
    - 2007-2011 Jun (Box 75, Folder 1)
  - Media Studies Journal
    - Winter 1999 (Box 81, Folder 3)
  - Mission Update
    Published in Washington, DC by the U.S. Catholic Mission Association (USCMA)
    - Vol. 1 no.1 (Mar./Apr. 1992), vol. 1 no. 3 (Jul./Aug. 1992)- no. 4 (Sep./Oct. 1992), vol. 2 no. 1 (Jan./Feb. 1992)- no. 5 (Nov/Dec. 1993), vol. 3 no. 2 (Mar/Apr. 1994)- no. 4 (Sep./Oct. 1994), vol. 4 no. 4 (Sep./Oct. 1995)- no. 5 (Nov./Dec. 1995), vol. 5 no. 1 (Jan./Feb. 1996), vol. 5 no. 3 (May/Jun. 1996), vol. 8 no. 1 (Spring 1999)-no. 3 (Autumn 1999) (Box 38, Folder 342-343)
    - Vol. 15 no. 1 (Spring 2006)- no. 4 (Winter 2006) (Box 53, Folder 428)
    - Vol. 16 no. 1 (Spring 2007) - no. 4 (Winter 2007) (Box 63, Folder 12)
  - Missions Etrangeres de Paris
    - 2009 Mar - 2009 Jun (Box 74, Folder 1)
    - 2009 Jul - 2009 Dec (Box 74, Folder 2)
    - 2010 Jan - 2010 May (Box 74, Folder 3)
    - 2010 Jul - 2010 Dec (Box 74, Folder 4)
    - 2011 Jan - 2011 May (Box 70, Folder 5)
  - National Committee on U.S.-China Relations
    - 2006-2011 (Box 70, Folder 3)
  - National Pastoral Center for the Chines Apostolate
    Published in New York, NY by NPCCA
    - No. 19 (Jan. 1996), no. 20 (Jun. 1996), no. 21 (Sep. 1996), no. 23 (Jul 1997), no. 24 (Mar. 1998) (Box 39, Folder 344)
  - The Networker
    Published in Washington, DC by the United States Catholic Conference
    - Vol. 4 no. 1 (Mar 1997)- no. 4. (Dec. 1997), vol. 5 no. 1 (Mar. 1998)- no. 2 (Jun 1998), vol. 6 no. 4 (Dec. 1998), vol. 7 no. 1 (Apr. 1999)- no. 2 (Jun 1999), vol. 9 no. 1 (Mar. 2001), (Mar- Dec 2003) (Box 39, Folder 345)
  - New Horizons
    Published in New York by United Board for Christian Higher Education in Asia
    - Vol. 58 no. 4 (Apr. 1991)-vol. 62 no. 3 (Summer 1995), vol. 63 no. 1 (Fall 1995-96); Also available at Divinity Library - Restricted Circulation Serial (Box 25, Folder 140)
    - Vol. 63 no. 2 (Winter/Spring 1996)- no. 3 (Summer 1996), vol. 64 no. 1 (Fall 1996)- no. 3 (Summer 1997), vol. 65 no. 1 (Fall 1997)- no. 3 (Summer 1998), vol. 66 no. 1 (Falll 1998)- no. 2 (Winter/Spring 1999), vo. 67 no. 1 (Fall 1999)- no. 2 (Winter/SPring 2000) (Box 39, Folder 346)
  - Newsweek
    Published in New York, NY
    - Jun. 29 1998 (Box 39, Folder 347)
  - New World Outlook
    Published in New York, NY by the General Board of Global Ministries of The United Methodist Church
    - Dates TBD (Box 39, Folder 348)
  - Pacific Rim Currents
    Published in San Francisco by University of San Francisco
    - Vol. 1 no. 1 (summer 1989), vol. 2 no. 1 (winter-spring 1990), vol. 2 no. 2 (fall-winter 1990-91), vol. 3 no. 1 (spring-summer 1991), vol. 4 no. 1 (spring-summer 1992), vol. 5 no. 1 (winter 1993), vol. 6 no. 2 (autumn 1993), vol. 7 no. 1 (autumn 1994), vol. 8 no. 1 (summer 1995) (Box 25, Folder 141-142)
    - Vol. 3 no. 9 (autumn 1996), no. 13 (summer 1997), no. 14 (winter 1998), no. 15 (Fall 1998), (2000-2001)- (2003-2004) (Box 39, Folder 351-352)
    - 2007-2010 (Box 70, Folder 3)
  - Pacific Rim Report
    - No. 12 (Mar. 2000)- no. 14 (Apr. 2000), no. 22 (May 2001)- no. 23 (Nov. 2001), no. 27 (Apr. 2003)- no. 30 (Nov. 2003) (Box 39, Folder 353)
    - Nos. 40-42 (Jun 2006) (Box 53, Folder 429)
    - Nos. 24, 32, 34, 36, 43 (2002-2007) (Box 63, Folder 13)
  - Passionist Heritage Newsletter
    Published in Union City, NJ by the Historical Commission of the Province of St. Paul of the Cross (Eastern U.S.A.)
    - Vol. 9 Nos. 3-4 (Summer, Fall 2002), Vol. 10 Nos. 1-2,4 (Winter, Spring, Fall 2003), Vol. 11 Nos. 3,4 (Summer, Fall 2004), Vo. 12 Nos. 2-3 (Spring, Summer 2005), Vol. 13 No. 2 (Spring 2006) (Box 63, Folder 14)
    - 2007-2011 (Box 76, Folder 5)
  - PIME World
    Published in Michigan by the PIME Missionaries
    - (Dec. 1992), (Feb 1995), (May 1995), (1996-1997), (Sep 1998) (Box 39, Folder 354)
  - Quest
    - 2002-2003, #1-2 (Box 82, Folder 1)
    - 2004, #1-2 (Box 82, Folder 2)
    - 2005, #1-2 (Box 82, Folder 3)
    - 2006-2007 (Box 82, Folder 4)
  - Regent Chinese Journal
    Published in Vancouver by Chinese Studies Program of Regent College
    - Vol. 2 no. 1 (1994), vol. 2 no. 2 (1994), vol. 2 no. 3 (1994), vol. 3 no. 1 (1995), vol. 3 no. 2 (1995), vol. 3 no. 3 (1995) (Box 25, Folder 143)
    - 1996, #1-3 (Box 73, Folder 1)
    - 1997, #1-3 (Box 73, Folder 2)
    - 1998, #1-3 (Box 73, Folder 3)
    - 1999, #1-2 (Box 73, Folder 4)
  - Religion in the People's Republic of China
    - 1980-1982, #2-9 (Box 91, Folder 5)
    - 1983-1984, #10-15 (Box 92, Folder 1)
    - 1985, #16-18 (Box 92, Folder 2)
  - The Ricci Bulletin
    - 1999-2000 & 2004 (Box 81, Folder 4)
  - Shijie Zong Jiao Ziliao
    - vol. 3-4 (1980), vol. 1-4 (1981), vol. 1-4 (1982), vol. 1-3 (1983), vol. 2-4 (1984), vol. 2 (1985), vol. 1,3-4 (1987) (Box 53–54)
  - Shijie Zong Jiao Ziliao Yan Jiu
    - vol. 1-4 (1987) (Box 54, Folder 435-436)
  - Spotlight on China
    - Vol. 39 no. 4 (Dec. 1996), vol. 40 no. 1 (Mar. 1997)- no. 4 (Dec. 1997), vol. 41 no. 1 (Mar. 1998)- no. 4 (Dec. 1998), vol. 42 no. 1 (Mar. 1999), no. 3 (Jun. 1999)- no. 4 (Sep. 1999), vol. 43 no. 1 (Dec. 1999)- no. 4 (Sep. 2000), vol. 44 no. 1 (Dec. 2000)- no. 4 (Sep. 2001), vol. 45 no. 1 (Dec. 2001)- no. 3 (Jun 2002), vol. 46 no. 1 (Dec. 2002)- no. 4 (Sep 2003), vol. 47 no. 1 (Dec. 2003)- no. 4 (Sep. 2004), vol. 48 no. 1 (Dec. 2004)- no. 4 (Sep. 2005) (Box 40, Folder 355-356)
  - Sunday Examiner
    Published in Hong Kong by Bishop of the Roman Catholic Church of Hong Kong
    - Vol. 50 no. 40, (Oct. 4, 1996), vol. 50 no. 41 (Oct. 11, 1996), vol. 50 no. 48 (Nov. 29, 1996)-vol. 51 no. 14 (Apr. 4, 1997), vol. 51 no. 16 (Apr. 18, 1997)-vol. 51 no. 40 (Oct. 5, 1997), vol. 51 no. 42 (Oct. 19, 1997)-vol. 51 no. 49 (Dec. 7, 1997), vol. 51 no. 51 (Dec. 21, 1997), vol. 52 no. 1 (Jan. 4, 1998)-vol. 52, no. 21 (May 24, 1998), vol. 52 no. 23 (June 7, 1998)-vol. 54 no. 5 (Jan. 30, 2000), vol. 54 no. 7 (Feb. 13, 2000)-vol. 55 no. 52 (Dec. 30, 2001) (Box 25–28)
    - vol. 56 no. 1 (Jan. 6, 2002)- no. 52 (Dec. 29, 2002), vol. 57 no. 1 (Jan. 5, 2003)- no. 52 (De. 25, 2003), vol. 58 no. 1 (Jan. 4, 2004)- no. 53 (Dec. 26, 2004), vol. 59 no. 1 (Jan 2, 2005)-no. 12 (Mar. 20, 2005), no. 14 (Apr. 3, 2005)- no. 52 (Dec. 25, 2005) (Box 40–42)
    - Vol. 60 (2006), Vol. 61 (2007 Jan-Aug) (Box 65, Folder 1, 2)
    - Vol. 61 (2007 Sep-Dec), Vol. 62 (2008) (Box 66, Folder 1-2)
    - 2009 Jan - 2009 Mar (Box 71, Folder 1)
    - 2009 Apr - 2009 Jun (Box 71, Folder 2)
    - 2009 Jul - 2009 Sep (Box 71, Folder 3)
    - 2009 Oct - 2009 Dec (Box 71, Folder 4)
    - 2010 Jan - 2010 Mar (Box 71, Folder 5)
    - 2010 Apr - 2010 Jun (Box 71, Folder 6)
    - 2010 Jul - 2010 Sep (Box 72, Folder 1)
    - 2010 Oct - 2010 Dec (Box 72, Folder 2)
    - 2011 Jan - 2011 Feb (Box 72, Folder 3)
    - 2011 Mar - 2011 May (Box 72, Folder 4)
    - 2011 Jun - 2011 Aug (Box 72, Folder 5)
  - Taiwan Church News
    (Uniform Title: Occasional bulletin [Presbyterian Church in Taiwan]); Published in Tainan, Taiwan by Taiwan Church News
    - Vol. 13 no. 1 (Jan/Feb 1996)-vol. 14 no. 1 (Jan/Feb 1997), vol. 14 no. 3 (May/June 1997)-vol. 18 no. 2 (Mar-Apr 2001), vol. 18 no. 5 (Sept-Oct 2001), vol. 19 no. 3 (May-June 2002); Also available at Divinity Library - Restricted Circulation Serial (Box 28, Folder 161-162)
    - Vol. 20 no.1 (Jan,Feb 2003)-no. 2 (Mar,Apr. 2003), nos. 4-6 (Jul- Dec. 2003), vol. 21 no. 1 (Jan-Feb 2004), no. 6 (Nov-Dec 2004) (Box 43, Folder 376)
  - Taiwan Communique (Washington D.C. edition)
    Published in Washington, DC by International Committee for Human Rights in Taiwan
    - No. 46 (Oct. 1990)-no. 64 (Jan. 1995), no. 66 (June 1995)-no. 68 (Oct. 1995); Also available at SML: JC 599 T28 (LC) (Box 28, Folder 163)
    - No. 69 (Jan. 1996)- no. 87 (Aug. 1999) (Box 43, Folder 377-378)
  - Tripod
    Published in Hong Kong, China by Holy Spirit Study Centre
    - 1981-1988 (Box 67, Folder 1-4)
    - 1989 - 1994, #80-84 (Box 68, Folder 1-4)
    - Vol. 11 no. 61 (Jan-Feb 1991)- vol. 12 no. 69 (May-Jun 1992), vol. 12 no. 71 (Sep.- Oct. 1992)- vol. 13 no. 75 (May- Jun 1993), vol. 13 no. 77 (Sep.- Oct. 1993)- vol. 14 no. 84 (Nov.- Dec. 1994), vol. 26 no. 140 (Spring 2006)- no. 143 (Winter 2006) (Box 55, Folder 437-440)
    - 1995, #85-90 - 2000, #117-120 (Box 69, Folder 1-5)
  - US-China Relations
    Published in New York, NY by the National Committee on United States-China Relations
    - Vol. 27 no. 1 (Summer/Fall 1998), vol. 28 no. 1 (Winter/Spring 1999)-no. 2 (Fall/Winter 1999), vol. 29 no. 1 (Spring/Summer 2000)- no. 2 (Fall/Winter 2000), vol. 30 no. 1 (Spring/ Summer 2001)- no. 2 (Fall/ Winter 2001), vol. 31 no. 2 (Fall/Winter 2002) (Box 43, Folder 379)
  - US-China Review
    Published in Los Angeles by US-China Peoples Friendship Association
    - Vol. 14 no. 1 (Winter 1990)-vol. 15 no. 1 (Winter 1991), vol. 15 no. 3 (Summer 1991), vol. 16 no. 1 (Winter 1992)-vol. 22 no. 4 (Fall 1998) [2 copies], vol. 23 no. 2 (Spring 1999)-vol. 24 no. 4 (Fall 2000); Also available at SML: E183.8 C5 U83 (LC)+ (Box 29, Folder 164-168)
    - Vol. 25 no. 1 (Winter 2001), vol. 27 no. 3 (Summer 2003), vol. 28 no. 1 (Winter 2004)- no. 4 (Fall 2004), vol. 29 no. 1 (Winter 2005)- no. 3 (Summer 2005) (Box 43, Folder 380-381)
    - Vol. 30, Nos. 3-4 (Summer, Fall 2006) (Box 64, Folder 7)
    - 2008-2009 (Box 76, Folder 8)
  - Voice of Friendship- Tokyo Chinese Catholic Community Newsletter
    Published by the Jesuit China Center
    - No. 43 (Feb. 2000)- no. 44 (Mar/Apr 2000), no. 50 (Mar/Apr 2001)- no. 61(Dec. 2003) (Box 43, Folder 382)
    - No. 62 (Apr. 2004)- no. 66 (Mar 2005), no. 69 (Apr. 2006)- no. 70 (Aug 2006) (Box 59, Folder 461)
  - Wei-Xin Newsletter
    Published in Hong Kong by Weixin
    - No.1 (Oct. 1985)-no.3 (Nov. 1986), no.5 (Feb. 1988)-no.11 (Mar. 1992) (Box 30, Folder 169)
  - Women of China
    Published in Beijing by Women of China
    - Issue 12 (1996) (Box 44, Folder 383)
  - Word & World
    - Spring 1997 (Box 81, Folder 3)
  - World Mission
    Published in Quezon City, M.M. Philippines by the Comboni Missionaries of the Heart of Jesus
    - Vol. 11 no. 6 (Jul 1999), vol. 11 no. 12 (Dec. 1999), vol. 12 no. 4 (Apr/May 2001), vol. 12 no. 5 (Jun. 2001)- no. 6 (Jul. 2001), vol. 12 no. 11 (Dec. 2001) (Box 44, Folder 384-385)
  - Yale-China Review
    - Vol. 1 no. 2 (Fall 1993), vol. 2 no. 1 (Summer 1994), vol. 3 no. 1 (Winter 1995), vol. 4 no. 1 (Spring 1996), vol. 4 no. 2 (Fall 1996); Also available at SML, Manuscripts and Archives (Non-Circulating), Yp37 + Y35 (Box 30, Folder 170)
  - Yi China Message
    Published in Hong Kong by "YI" Editorial Board
    - Vol. 8 no. 5 (Oct. 1989), vol. 8 no. 6 (Dec. 1989), vol. 9 no. 3 (June 1990), vol. 9 no. 6 (Dec. 1990), vol. 10 no. 1 (Feb. 1991)- vol. 13 no. 3 (Apr. 1994), vol. 13 no. 6 (Aug. 1994)-vol. 14 no. 10 (Dec. 1995)vol. 15-17 no. 6 (Aug. 1996), vol. 15-17 no. 9 (Nov. 1996), vol. 15-17 no. 10 (Dec. 1996) (Box 30, Folder 171-174)
    - Vol. 18 no. 1 (Jan-Fev. 1997)- vol. 19 no. 6 (Jul. 1998), vol. 19 no. 8 (Sep.-Oct. 1998)- no. 199-200 (Mar-Jun. 2005) (Box 44, Folder 386-387)
    - vol. 75 no 7 (1987)- vol. 76 no. 8 (1987), vol. 84 no. 5-6 (1988)- vol. 89-90 no. 11/12 (1988) Chinese language; vol. 5 no. 6 (1986), vol. 7 no. 2 (Apr. 1988)- vol. 8 no. 4 (Aug 1989); vol. 92 no. 3 (1989)- vol. 103 no. 3 (1990); vol. 9 no. 1 (Feb 1990)- no. 2 (Apr. 1990), no. 4 (Aug 1990)- no. 5 (Oct 1990), vol. 12 no. 4 (May-Jun 1994), vol. 13 no. 5 (Jul 1994), vol. 15-17 no. 4 (May 1996) (Box 59, Folder 462-466)
    - Vol. 21 Nos. 197/198, 201-205 (Sep 2004 - Sep 2006) (Box 64, Folder 8)
  - Zhonglian
    Published: Paris by l'Association RELAIS FRANCE-CHINE
    - No. 70 (Dec. 1996)-no. 102 (Aug.-Oct. 2002) (Box 30, Folder 175-176)
    - No. 103 (Dec. 2002)- no. 106 (Jun. 2003), no. 108 (Dec. 2003)-no. 118 (Dec. 2005) (Box 44, Folder 388)
    - No. 119 (Feb. 2006)- no. 123 (Dec. 2006) (Box 60, Folder 467)
    - 2007-2008 (Box 76, Folder 7)
- Program Activities, 2001-2005; Series II
  - 20th National Catholic China Conference Proceedings: the Role of Religion in China's Emerging Civil Society, 2003 (Box 30, Folder 177)
  - USCCB News (United States Conference of Catholic Bishops); News notices from various publications, 2002-2006 (Box 56–58)
  - 21st National Catholic Conference: The Growth of Christianity in China: Realities, Challenges, Opportunities - Seattle University, 2005 Jun 24-26 (Box 66, Folder 3)
  - 20th Anniversary of Educational Services Exchange with China - event program, 2001 (Box 94, Folder 3)